This is a great guessing game.
You need a minimum of two people to play this game.
How you play is, you choose one person who's going to be the patient and anyone else who's there are going to play the psychiatrists.
So you can have one or several psychiatrists in your game.
The patient chooses something they're deathly afraid of - a big phobia, a big fear - and we have to try and guess what their fear is.
They can't tell us but we can ask questions and through process of elimination we have to figure out what their phobia is.
When we guess it, then we become the patient.
Teri: Are you ready?
Do you have one in your head?
David: Uh huh.
Teri: Okay.
So is what you're afraid of in this room right now?
David: It might be.
Teri: What do you mean there might be?
Are they small?
David: They can be, yea.
Teri: Can they also be large?
David: Yes.
Teri: What color would they be, if there was one?
David: Black, gray, and gross.
Teri: Oh, Ah.
Is it when people don't clean their house too well?
Do you see a lot of these?
David: Yes Teri: Are you afraid of dust?
David: No Teri: Dust bunnies?
David: No.
Teri: Something similar to that though?
David: Yes.
Teri: Okay, mud?
David: No.
Teri: Okay, well you say if... David: Where did you get your psychiatrist degree?
Teri: Ah, back in Ohio..State University.
David: You're terrible.
Teri: Sorry.
Um, where would I find these other than in this house?